<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>TomoCodes</title><description></description><link>https://tomo.codes</link><atom:link
    href="https://tomo.codes/feed.rss"
    rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"
/><language>en</language><generator>Ignite v0.6.0</generator><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://tomo.codes/building-swift-package-with-xcodebuild</guid><title>Packages, resources, and the fine print</title><link>https://tomo.codes/building-swift-package-with-xcodebuild</link><description><![CDATA[As I am working on this site (which is build using Ignite) I am encountering interesting problems I haven’t faced on a daily basis working with projects in Xcode. Initially I have started working using Xcode, however as I needed to interact with different file types (like markdown) I finally switched to Visual Studio Code. Before I did that however I had already sprinkled this project with Xcode conveniences. One of those especially being assets catalog (*.xcassets). I was not only blessed with visual format for working with colors, but at the same time brought compile time safety with ColorResource. Cats and rainbows everywhere!]]></description><pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomasz Lizer]]></dc:creator><category><![CDATA[tip]]></category><category><![CDATA[swift package]]></category><category><![CDATA[xcodebuild]]></category></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://tomo.codes/mac-os-keyboard-navigation</guid><title>Tab, Space, Done</title><link>https://tomo.codes/mac-os-keyboard-navigation</link><description><![CDATA[How often have you stumbled on some dialog in your flow that completely destroys it? Maybe there is no preselected option, or the one that is highlighted is not the one you want to go with? Recently as I try to stay on keyboard as long as possible I started hitting the wall in some places. Context change from keyboard to mouse is slow and inefficient and it started bothering me. My typical breakpoint of such type is file deletion in Xcode. Depending on the file type you will be deleting you can face one of those dialogs:]]></description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><dc:creator><![CDATA[Tomasz Lizer]]></dc:creator><category><![CDATA[tip]]></category><category><![CDATA[productivity]]></category><category><![CDATA[macos]]></category></item></channel></rss>